thehouseofdrew.com 2019-12-23

# Privacy Policy – Drew House

Welcome to the Drew House website located at [thehouseofdrew.com](https://thehouseofdrew.com/) _ _ and other related domains. We believe that the privacy and security of your information and data is very important. This Privacy Policy explains the type of information we collect from users of the Website, how that Information is used, how the Information may be shared with other parties, and what controls our users have regarding their Information. We encourage you to read this Policy carefully. Any updates or modifications to this Policy will be posted to our website on this page. By using or accessing the Website, you signify that you have read, understand and agree to be bound by this Policy. This Policy is effective as of December 5, 2018 __ and has not been modified since that date.

Information We Collect

There are two types of Information that may be collected through our Website: (1) "Personal Information" which is information that can be used to directly identify you such as your name, e-mail address, physical address, phone number, and credit card number, and (2) "Usage Data" which is anonymous information not linked to you personally that is related to your use of the Website, including information about the computer and mobile device you use when visiting the Website, (e.g., your unique device ID, Internet Protocol (IP) address, or other persistent identifiers), as well as data regarding your activity, such as the actions you take within and outside of the Website, the browser and/or device you use, and the date and time of your use of the Website.

You may enter the Website and browse its contents without submitting any Personal Information. However, if you wish to establish an account, make a purchase, contact us, subscribe to our newsletter or other mailings, post any comments, participate in certain promotions, or otherwise communicate with us, whether through our Website, our social media pages or any of our e-mail addresses, we may at that time require that you provide Personal Information or give you the ability to provide Personal Information. When you submit Personal Information in any manner, you are giving your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

If you choose to connect to our Website through a third-party social network such as Facebook (each, a "Social Network"), we may collect Personal Information from your profile on such Social Network, such as your name, username, and e-mail address, and we may publish your activity on our Website through such Social Network. In addition, our Website may offer social sharing features which will allow you to "Share" or "Like" on a Social Network. If you decide to use such features, it may allow the sharing and collection of Information both to and from such Social Network so you should check the privacy policy of each Social Network before using such features.

Whether or not you submit Personal Information, whenever you visit the Website, click on our advertisements (including those appearing on third party sites), or visit our social media pages, we or our Service Providers (as defined below) may collect, store or accumulate certain Usage Data based on your use of our Website, such as information regarding which of our pages or products are most popular, the browser you use, your computer's IP address, and the URLs you visited before and after using our Website. For more information on how this Usage Data is collected, please see the Cookies section below.

Please note that we will only collect your credit card information if you choose to purchase our products online via our Website. If you do make such an online purchase, our payment processing partner will collect your payment information and process your payment. We do not store any credit card information or share it with anyone other than our payment processor.

Uses and Sharing of Information

We use the Personal Information that we collect to process your requests, fulfill your orders, authenticate website visits/usage, inform you of relevant products and specials through promotional e-mails, maintain and develop our Website, and otherwise communicate with you. You always will be given the opportunity to unsubscribe from further emails in any promotional messages we send you. If you would like to preemptively opt out of receiving any communications from us, please e-mail us and include "Opt Out" in the subject line.

Except as described above, we will not disclose, rent, sell or share any Personal Information to unaffiliated third parties for direct marketing purposes.

We do contract with companies or individuals to provide us and you with certain services including email and hosting services, software development, credit card processing, shipping, fulfillment, data management, surveys and marketing, promotional services, etc. We call them our "Service Providers." We may share both your Personal Information and Usage Data with Service Providers solely as required for them to perform their functions. We do not share your credit card or other account information with third parties unless you authorize us to do so, or if it is necessary to fulfill our responsibilities including, but not limited to, delivering a product or service that you order.

In addition, aggregated, non-personally-identifiable Usage Data may be used by us, or shared with our Service Providers for use, in connection with general operational, administrative, advertising, analytical, research, optimization, and security purposes, but no such information will be linked with your Personal Information or be used to identify or contact you. For more information about how Usage Data may be used for interest-based advertising, please see the section entitled "Targeted Advertising" below.

Finally, we may share your Information: (i) In response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases we reserve the right to raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us; (ii) When we believe it is appropriate to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal or suspected illegal activities; to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of our company, our users, or others; and in connection with our Terms of Use and other agreements; or (iii) In connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

Privacy and Security

It is entirely your choice whether or not you provide Personal Information to us. We take reasonable precautions to protect our customers' Personal Information against loss, misuse, unauthorized disclosure, alteration, and destruction. However, please remember that no transmission of data over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us or from us, and you do so at your own risk. You hereby acknowledge that we are not responsible for any intercepted information sent via the Internet, and you hereby release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of intercepted information in any unauthorized manner.

In addition, while we take reasonable steps to govern our Service Providers' use and protection of your Personal Information, we ultimately have no control over and are not responsible for the privacy practices of such parties. As a condition to your use of the Website, you expressly agree we bear no responsibility, and are not liable in any way, for the acts, omissions or policies of our Service Providers or any other external sources with respect to your Information

If you believe your Personal Information is being improperly used by us or any third party, please immediately notify us via email.

Cookies

As part of our collection and use of Usage Data (as described in more detail herein), we, or our Service Providers, may use cookies, web beacons, tracking pixels, or similar tracking technologies. These "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Generally, Cookies work by assigning to your computer a unique number that has no meaning outside of the Website but can be used to gather Usage Data. While Cookies may record certain persistent identifiers related to your computer or device, they do not contain any Personal Information.

Most web browsers automatically accept Cookies, but you can usually configure your browser to prevent this. However, not accepting Cookies may make certain features of the Website unavailable to you.

Targeted Advertising

We engage certain third party ad network Service Providers to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet and to provide analytics services. These entities may utilize Cookies (including within the ads) to collect Usage Data from you such as your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, how you use our Website, items you put in your basket, any links you click on, and conversion information. This information may be used by us and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content or products, measure the effectiveness of ad campaigns, determine the proper amount of repeat views of a given ad, and deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our websites and other websites (also known as "interest-based advertising").

Children Under 13

This website is targeted to adults. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information directly from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you are a parent or guardian of a child under 13 years of age and you believe your child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us.

Opting Out

When registering for an account on our Website, you will have the ability to "opt in" to receiving further promotional communications from us. Alternatively, if you initially decide to receive information from us but at a later date wish to remove your information from our database, you can do so by using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our emails. You may also at any time opt out of receiving e-mails from us or our affiliated or related companies by sending an e-mail with the subject line "Opt Out."

Please note that even if you unsubscribe from our promotional email messages, we may still need to contact you with important transactional information related to your account and your purchases. For example, even if you have unsubscribed from our promotional emails, we will still send you confirmation of a purchase you have made on our Website.

Links to Third Party Websites

Our Website or emails may contain links to third party websites to which we have no affiliation (including social networks). Except as set forth in this Policy, we do not share your Personal Information with those websites and are not responsible for the privacy policies of any other website or their management of your Personal Information. Because they may treat your Information differently than we do, we suggest you read the privacy policies on those third party websites prior to submitting any Personal Information.

Your Rights and Obligations

We ask that you keep the Personal Information that you provide to us current and that you correct any information you have provided us by contacting us. You represent and warrant that all Personal Information you provide us is true and correct and relates to you and not to any other person.

If you wish to review, delete and/or revise the Personal Information we have stored about you, please contact us with your specific request; provided, however, that we reserve the right to retain an archive of such Personal Information for a commercially reasonable time to ensure that its deletion does not affect the integrity of our data; and we further reserve the right to retain an anonymous version of such Information.

If you use the Website, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and for restricting access to your computer or device, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account.

Your California Privacy Rights

Under certain circumstances, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 states that, upon receipt of a request by a California customer, a business may be required to provide detailed information regarding how that business has shared that customer's personal information with third parties for direct marking purposes. However, the foregoing does not apply to businesses like ours that do not disclose Personal Information to third parties for direct marketing purposes without prior approval or give customers a free mechanism to opt out of having their personal information disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. California users may request further information about their rights under this law and our policy by writing to us, using the subject line "CA Request for Information," and requesting further information.

California Do Not Track Disclosures: For a variety of reasons, including technical limitations, our Website and our Service Providers may not recognize browser "Do Not Track" signals.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time. In the event we make material changes to this Policy, such policy will be re-posted in the "Privacy" section of our Website with the date such modifications were made indicated on the top of the page. Therefore, please review this Policy from time to time so that you are aware when any changes are made to this Policy. If you have any questions about the changes that were implemented, please contact us and include "Information Regarding Updated Policy" in the subject line. In any event, your continued use of the Website after such change constitutes your acceptance of any such change(s), and if you do not accept any changes, you may choose not to use the Website or opt out by sending us an appropriate notice.

General Legal

All other terms governing this Privacy Policy shall be those set forth in our Terms of Use which are incorporated herein by this reference.

If you have questions or comments about this Policy, please contact us with "Website Privacy" in the subject line of your email.
